[
    {
        "Question": "How does idev work?",
        "Answer Given": "How it works { works }",
        "Score": 0.13670626282691956,
        "Actual Answer": "submits a batch job that creates a copy of the batch environment"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does idev do?",
        "Answer Given": "creates an interactive development environment from the user's login window",
        "Score": 0.3465190529823303,
        "Actual Answer": "creates and interactive development environment from the user's login window"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the terminal command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "ibrun",
        "Score": 0.024445416405797005,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the command for idev?",
        "Answer Given": "exit",
        "Score": 0.2282835990190506,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How much time will the system report the job status?",
        "Answer Given": "every 4 seconds",
        "Score": 0.6628867387771606,
        "Actual Answer": "every 4 seconds"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What happens on the first time launching idev?",
        "Answer Given": "you have multiple projects/allocations",
        "Score": 0.4542042315006256,
        "Actual Answer": "idev will prompt you for the project name and then save your selection as the default interactive account"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do you start an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "Stampede3 Skylake development node",
        "Score": 0.27365827560424805,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "How do launch an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "your first time",
        "Score": 0.07994014769792557,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which command launces an idev session?",
        "Answer Given": "ibrun",
        "Score": 0.32611218094825745,
        "Actual Answer": "idev"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What does -m do with idev",
        "Answer Given": "m   minutes            sets time in minutes",
        "Score": 0.05019431933760643,
        "Actual Answer": "sets time in minutes"
    }
]